Mangoba, John Carlo Apolinario APPLICANT



CONTACT

Cabanatuan City, Philippines 3100

09626081213

mangobajohncarlo@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am John Carlo Apolinario Mangoba. 23 years of age, a Computer Engineering graduate from Wesleyan University -Philippines. I have an optimistic attitude towards life and I am an outgoing person. I like to sing and play guitar. I do work with enthusiasm.

EXPERIENCE

Work Immersion February 2020 to March 2020 Engineering Department Phinma Araullo University Cabanatuan City, Nueva Ecija

On-the-Job Training Department of Agrarian Reform June 2023 to September 2023 Cabanatuan City, Nueva Ecija

SKILLS AND INTEREST

- Programming skills
- Computer systems knowledge
- MS Office
- UI/UX design skills (HTML, CSS and js)
- Basic Networking

CORE STRENGTHS

- Strong knowledge of programming languages and real-world coding experience.
- Ability to explain complex ideas in simple and clear ways.
- Good communication skills and adaptable to different learning styles.
- Fast learner, able to quickly adapt to new tools, technologies, and teaching methods.

EDUCATION

Wesleyan University - Philippines
Bachelor of Science in Computer
Engineering 2020 to 2024

Phinma Araullo University

Junior Highschool to Senior Highschool 2014 to 2020

Mabini Homesite Elementary School

Elementary Education 2008 to 2014

CERTIFICATES

Frontend Fundamentals bootcamp (One Code camp - Aug 2024)

Headless CMS: Empowering Web Development

Building a stronger You: A Guide to Personality Development

Bronze Awardee ANP - Rookie Advisor Level

REFERENCE

Atty. Maranatha Joy Osorio-Pelayo Lawyer 0923 273 1736

Frederick R. Manlusoc Computer Engineer 0968 852 5629

Israel Osorio Court Legal Researcher 09062762516